Friends, did you also buy a bike on installment?  Have you bought
any car on installment like Honda
Splendor Sin or TVS, any
car of Bajaj or any other company and
you want to check its installment.  You
should also check how much EMI is left.
Because you know how much confusion there is in today's time.
So here we should also check
how much installment is left for us.  How much have
we accumulated?  If you also
want to check and know in this way
then stay tuned to this video.  I will teach you everything
, tell you everything about how you
can find out how much loan is left on your car.
How much have you deposited?  How to
check everything like EMI etc.
How to know everything, we will give you information in this video.
I will tell you everything in detail.
So let's move ahead in this video.  Let's
learn everything.  Let us know.  So hello
and welcome friends you are watching Android
Junction YouTube channel and my name is
Rupesh.  Friends, let's start today
's video.  And yes friends, on this channel
we keep bringing such valuable content
for you daily.  So please
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
Let's move ahead.  Friends
[nasal sound] do you also
want to check your car installment EMI
?  So how will we do it?  Let us tell you.
Like first of all you have to
come to Google Play Store and go to the search bar.  First of all,
you have to check your company
from which company you have finance.
Like [nasal sound]
suppose if you are from Bajaj then you will get
an app called Bajaj Finance app
i.e. Bajaj Finserv.
You have to download this.  If you have a loan from TVS, then
here comes an app called TVS Credit.
You have to download it here.
Ok?  This is how to load it.  Like
mine is from Hero Fincrap so I
will download Hero Fincrap from here.  Ok?  Let
me show you the first one in Hero Fincrap.
Then I will tell you in each app how you will be
able to know your loan installment, how much
is left, how much is deposited.  So I downloaded this application and
opened it.  Similarly, you will also have to
download and open it.
[nasal sound] Then you have to
allow permission from here.  Ok?  And here
you
can login to the application through your mobile number or
through the loan application number.
So I have the loan application number
so I will click on the loan application number
and fill in my loan application number from here.
I gave my loan number and
clicked on verify number and as soon as I
click on verify number, I will click on send OTP
and when I click on send OTP,
an OTP will come on my number.  So
similarly OTP will come on your number also.  So the
OTP has to be filled here.  Ok?
And as soon as you fill the OTP here, it will take only a
few seconds and you will be
logged into this app.  So as soon as the OTP
comes, we fill it and then
move forward.  OTP has come on our number, we will
click on Continue to Login and
as soon as we click, we will be logged in, we will continue
from here.  We will
allow the permission and if any such tutorial comes, we will
skip it.  We will click on Not Now
and such an option will load in front of us.
As you can see.  Like the
installment that comes to me is of this amount.
As you can see here.
And when [nasal sound]
you come down, there will be an option right here for
loan status.  If you click on this, you will
get complete information about the loan.  How much is the installment and
when is our next EMI.  How much loan amount did I
take?  And here, if we
click on View Loan Summary, it will be
told that I had taken this much loan and the
installment is of this much and the total EMI
I had taken was this much and
I have deposited this much EMI and this much is still to be deposited
and [nasal sound] if we
click on View Loan Detail, then the complete
[sound of clearing throat] details will open
like at what percentage it was taken,
how it is, what will be the date of EMI,
all this information will be given here
and how many installments are paid and how many are unpaid,
all this will be shown and
[nasal sound] the complete details will be available
here.  So you can see that
I have taken out the complete details from here and
you can also find out your details in this way.  There is nothing else to
do.  Just
like I logged in, you
can also login to your loan app in the same way.
If you are a Bajaj user then you have to come to this app.  If you are a
TVS user then you have to come to this app.
Otherwise, if you are
financing from any other [sound of clearing throat] app
then please comment me.  I will
make a video on that.  So see you
[nasal sound]
in another video.  Till then, you all take
good care of yourselves.  Bye bye
friends.